<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://sharora.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://sharora.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-07-06T11:01:01+00:00</updated><id>https://sharora.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">sharora.github.io</title><subtitle>A blog documenting my personal projects and rambling about random topics.</subtitle><author><name>Shreyas Arora</name><email>.</email></author><entry><title type="html">blog reborn</title><link href="https://sharora.github.io/meta/2023/07/03/new-beginnings.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="blog reborn" /><published>2023-07-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-07-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://sharora.github.io/meta/2023/07/03/new-beginnings</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://sharora.github.io/meta/2023/07/03/new-beginnings.html"><![CDATA[<hr />

<p>For the past several years I have flirted with the idea of starting a blog.
Every time school goes on break or the pressure from work and activities eases a
bit I think to myself, wouldn’t it be cool to immortalize all the dumb ideas in
my head just so that in the off chance someone reads them in the future they too
can realize how stupid I am. Then I proceed to waste all my free time searching
for the perfect blogging framework and when I finally do I’m out of time and I
have to attend to actually “important” things again.</p>

<p>In all seriousness, I did end up starting a pseudonymous blog a couple years ago
on which I posted a handful of times. I chose this route initially because I
wanted the freedom anonymity provides; I can write about any topic freely and
open up in a way that I have never been able to do talking with anyone before.
However keeping the blog anonymous creates a couple of issues. Firstly since my
name isn’t attached to the blog there is much less pressure to write anything of
measurable quality (not claiming I can do this even with my name attached).
Secondly there is a conflict of interest as in some cases I do want my name to
be attached to my work like when I am writing about a technical topic or a
personal project. The anonymity means that although I can write about some more
personal topics, I can never write about anything connecting the blog directly
to myself.</p>

<p>As a result my motivation to write on that blog has fizzled out so I have closed
it and decided to start fresh here. This time in order to address the above
issues I am attaching this blog to my real name. This does mean that I won’t be able
to write about some topics but I’m okay with that.</p>

<p>I have a couple ideas lined up to write about this summer so lets hope this time
this time when I kick start the blog the engine keeps running. Thanks for reading
and see you next time!</p>]]></content><author><name>Shreyas Arora</name><email>.</email></author><category term="meta" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry></feed>